Guide to the Joel Shurkin Interviews for His Book, Engines of the Mind
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Joel Shurkin interviews for his book, Engines of the Mind
1977-1982
SC1149
Shurkin, Joel N., 1938-
0.5 Linear feet (14 audiocassettes)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Joel Shurkin, April 1985.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Associated Materials
Engines of the Mind http://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/1067766
Access Terms
Audiotapes.; Computer scientists--California.; Computers--History.; Interviews.
Collection Contents
- Interviews
  - Eckert, J. Presber, 1982 Jun 18; 2 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Burks, Arthur, 1982 Dec 23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Huskey, Harry, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Terry, Duncan Niles, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Brainard, John, Undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Atanasoff, John Vincent, 1982 Jun 19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Averbach, Ike, 1982 Jun 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Goldstein, H.; Amber, Kay Mauchley, 1982 Jan 11-12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Mauchley, John, 1977; 5 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)